[Music]
Welcome back to my channel and this is R
race with casy and first of all here on
our page we are talking about
money issues career and
our dreams in life so join me on
our Journey to learn and
face the challenges of life so that we can
be better stewards of the
blessings of our Lord All right
and in this video we will
talk about common sections
or misconceptions about life
insurance and don't worry I can relate
to that because I was also stressed
before and now Thank God for
lightening us up about life insurance and
now you know join me to
enjoy the benefits of life
insurance which is the most expensive one
of the most expensive things in the world
which is peace of mind so number one
common misconception about life
insurance is that it is only for the
rich if you are rich then
go ah I realized it doesn't
benefit the poor more
and you can Actually start small It doesn't
need to be so expensive
Actually there is  200 per month 300 per
month and imagine that if we can have
coffee for How much is coffee
100 then 100 times how many times do you
have coffee in a month I'm guilty of that,
right?
So we can afford maybe
Php2,000 for coffee per month we can afford
life insurance if
we have a cigarette butt cigarettes are expensive now
last time
I had a cigarette backend details it's been a long time now
What else is PH 45 now I don't know how
much a all I know is it's expensive
now The price of
cigarettes you drink is far from the previous price no so imagine how
much we spend on
these things to give us temporary
happiness like that or certain days but um
we haven't considered this life
insurance is we will give us peace of
mind especially peace of mind of
our loved ones Just in case
something happens to us
Lord will take us or we get sick so we won't
be a burden to our families
especially if we are really struggling
and poor in life So
we can set aside at least  a small amount
no even if we just take a
policy for this year then we'll just do whatever we want Let
's just renew next year Then
when of course we move forward
then we'll be better
next year so maybe next year
we can afford the bigger Ah bigger Ah
bigger policy the better policy
So that's one of the flaws of life
insurance is that it's only for the rich
so we should think about that thought
even if it's just a little bit
we can afford now um Let's make this one of
our priorities because that's it It gives us
Ah one of the most expensive things in the world
which is peace of mind and we won't
be a Burden to our
Kapamilyas second common misconception
about life insurance is it is a scam
well life insurance um there are
probably people like Agents who are
um
dependent There are people like that Of course they
will take the money they won't
put it in the right
Ah they won't return it to the company like that
there are people like that and the people who don't
really have the intention of helping their
clients Yes it can be a scam but the
life insurance
since I didn't understand him that's how
I look at it
I'll just take my money from this TS
I won't get anything In The End so he's not like
that and that's why it's easier for us It's
easier for us to
dota goal of gr and gra with KC because
we'll understand our um things more as
adults There's a lot I still do
n't understand about this in my lungs I don't
understand why it's necessary to
get a valid ID you also need a
fake ID so that's There are things that
we really need to make an effort to
understand so life insurance is not a scam
there are Maybe there are
companies that are really going under or
going bankrupt that's why but it's not a scam
because it works it works Many people have
benefited from that and
Actually maybe it's just here in the
Philippines it's not very popular
especially in the provinces here in
our province like that It's not
talked about much but in the other countries
it's it's a necessity It's part of the
necessity of life No so he's not a
scam number three common misconceptions
about life insurance and Here
I'm really guilty no I don't need him
because I'm healthy
MM because that's According to you
um you're too confident I said
I supported you  I'm mindful of my
best interests, I'm not careless.
I don't really have anything like that.
But we don't know. We don't
know how long we'll be in this
world. And we don't know if we suddenly get
sick out of nowhere. Like for example,
I'm just good at getting sick and
who would have thought I'd get sick.
That person. Why don't you know?
Until when? Only God Knows how long
we'll be in this world. You
can tell your parents, you don't
know. So it's better to
get life insurance when
we're healthy because we can't get
approved. We have a lot of
health conditions.
We have a lot of illnesses. Okay. There are only rare
cases that are approved. Those who have
serious illnesses. They're
there. We're healthier. We
should get it as early as that. Number
four, the misconception about life
insurance is that there are
many things that need to be studied. And
I said, I won't
let you in. It's necessary. It's important. That's
right. Maybe it's just to me. It
seems like it's necessary.
I really need it.  spend a
lot of time, it's like I'm not N
is
but when that's when we focused, ah, I'm still lazy,
just focus, but what's the matter,
you're open-minded to do new
things, the realities of life, so the
more the most open-minded, good, how it
works, I've studied a little bit,
because I'm an adult, you're a client,
and then your client is sincere, it will
help, SAO, there's even one seat, there's
no question,
we need to answer your
questions, we are
yours in your
life and also there's a common misconception
that there's nothing,
oh, what's that, if you just die,
where will you die, so our mind is still thinking,
but I also hesitated to just
focus on the
man, sick, mine, work, Andal,
illness, Ben, when there's an accident, there's
retirement, and Um, you want
to not be a burden on your
children or your grandchildren, you have
money to enjoy
your retirement age, which you don't know,
you know, the downfall in life because
you've saved, you've saved, right?
and then there is also a Focus on
educational, you know, you have a child, um,
what about 2 years old, 3 years old, like
that, you can apply for
her and or his education or preparation, that's
also it. Just in case, no, um, 10 years
from now, 5 years from now,
you don't know what's going to happen, you don't know. Like
for example, a pandemic, you have no
preparation, or so, we have no preparation,
we have no savings, so
life is hard for you, let's go
and then, I'm just for the elderly, young people,
because you're young,
your premium is cheaper, and
if you take out investment-
related insurance, it's bigger.
Your accumulation would have been bigger
now, it started earlier if
you were older. You have a lot of money, you have a lot of debt, it's
harder to really get hurt.
How expensive will it be?
and last but not the least, a
common misconception about life
insurance is that it's only for
breadwinners, so it's okay for me not to
buy insurance because I'm not
the main source of income for our
family. No, but if you are alive and
have a loved one, No.  it's good that
we have our own life insurance too because
that's our Goal we don't we don't we don't
know what can happen to the
bed winner we don't know how
big the impact of our
disablement or our illness or our
death will be on our loved ones and
it's good that we have a Back up
plan So that's um for your peace of
mind for the peace of mind of your
family we won't be a
Burden we won't be drowning in debt our
assets in life when we are gone
and taken by the
lord So It's good bad winner or
not it's good to have life insurance
and the best time is as soon as
possible actually it's not just a
marketing strategy that's what
I realized as soon as possible if
we have to give up Even if it's just a little
no Even if it's just a little of our h
extra extra iss spend on
food on clothes or what why not
um let's invest it in life insurance
because that's it's for us and for our
family and if somehow
you have something to learn or you have been inspired or
you know there is  Just think of
this video, please don't forget
to like and subscribe to our page and to
share if
you like it, so that you can also help
me continue it videos to educate
our Filipinos about
money matters, career matters and
our dreams in life so that we can
be what we are. We can
grow together. We can be successful and we can
be good towards God's blessings.
Thank you.
[Applause]